Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
- 1. Research Files, 1973-1993
  - Elvis Presley Programs, 1984-1993
    - Presley Research - Sessions with Gordon Stoker, undated
    - Elvis Special - Notes from 1956 Interview, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Various - Notes, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Allen, Steve, undated
    - Presley Research - Asner, Ed, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Boone, Pat, undated
    - Fabares, Shelley, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Gatlin, Larry, undated
    - Geller, Larry, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Golden, George, undated
    - Howe, Bones, undated
    - Kanter, Hal, undated
    - Lange, Hope, undated
    - Martindale, Wink, undated
    - Presley Research - Nielsen, Shaun, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Schilling, Jerry, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Smith, Myrna, 1993
    - Presley Interviews - Thompson, Sam, undated
    - Weisman, Ben, undated
    - Presley Interviews - Westmopeland, Kathy, undated
  - Rolling Stones Programs, 1973-1989
    - Jagger, Mick - Articles, undated (Box 66)
    - Richards, Keith - Articles, undated
    - Rolling Stones - "211 Reasons Why…" - Pamphlet, undated
    - Rolling Stones - 20/20 Transcripts, 1989 September 22
    - Rolling Stones - 25th Anniversary Special, 1989 October
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1973
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1976
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1978
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1981
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1982
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1983
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1985
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1986
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1987
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1988
    - Rolling Stones - Articles, 1990
    - Rolling Stones - Chronology/Discography, 1986, 1989
    - Rolling Stones - Publicity Photos, 1980 December 27
    - Rolling Stones - Steel Wheels Tour, undated
    - Watts, Charlie, undated
    - Wood, Ron - Articles, 1988 September 27
  - General Subject Files, undated
    - African American Athletes, undated (Box 67)
    - African American Entertainers - Ailey, Alvin, undated
    - African American Entertainers - Hall, Arsenio, undated
    - African American Entertainers - Blake, Eubie, undated
    - African American Enterainers - Carter, Thomas II, undated
    - African American Enterainers - Horne, Lena, undated
    - African American Enterainers - Johnson, Foster, undated
    - African American Entertainers - Nicholas, Fayard and Harold, undated
    - African American Entertainers - Stewart, Nick, undated
    - African American Entertainers - Tucker, Lorenzo, undated
    - African American Enterainers - Soul & Doo-wop Musicians, undated
    - African American Writers, undated
    - African Americans - Classical Music, undated
    - African Americans - History, undated
    - Apollo Theater, undated
    - Archive of Contemporary Music, undated
    - Benefits - Amnesty International, undated
    - Benefits - Band Aid, undated
    - Benefits - Can-Aid, undated
    - Benefits - Farm Aid, undated
    - Benefits - Hear 'N Aid, undated
    - Benefits - Live Aid, undated
    - Benefits - Miscellaneous, undated
    - Benefits - Prince's Trust, undated
    - Benefits - Romanian Angel Appeal, undated
    - Comedians - Miscellaneous, undated
    - Festivals - Us Festival, undated
    - Festivals - Woodstock, undated
    - Festivals - Long Beach Blues Festival, undated
    - Music Videos - Miscellaneous, undated
    - Music Videos - MTV Awards, undated
    - Night of the Guitar Live, undated
    - Producers - Miscellaneous, undated
    - Record Labels - Atlantic, undated
    - Record Labels - Capitol, undated
    - Record Labels - Chess, undated
    - Record Labels - Elektra, undated
    - Record Labels - Epic, undated
    - Record Labels - Liberty, undated
    - Record Labels - No Speak, undated
    - Record Labels - Polygram, undated
    - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, undated
    - Rock Music International, undated
    - Rock Music Veterans, undated
    - Rockabilly, undated
    - Scream, undated
    - Shearer, Karen - Book Proposal (with Jean Kasem), undated
    - Shearer, Karen - Westwood One Correspondence (Rock Chronicles & CT40), undated
    - Soundtracks, undated
    - Soundtracks - Civil War, undated
    - Soundtracks - Goya, undated
    - Soundtracks - House Party, undated
    - Terry Marshall's Daily Insider, undated